(Leonard:)Yeah, no, I got it.
(Bernadette:)-So how's your experiment going?
-Terrific.
(Leonard:)Getting the electron accelerator set up.
We should be ready day after tomorrow.
(Bernadette:)-Boy, I'd love to see that.
-You're welcome to come.
Really? That'd be great.
(Bernadette:)How exciting is that?
(Howard:)Like Hanukkah in July.
(Bernadette:)Do they have that?
(Sheldon:)-No.
-Oh, you got me again.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
(Bernadette:)This isn't non-fat yogurt.
This is fatty-fat fat.
(Bernadette:)Excuse me.
-Could you grab me another napkin?
-Sure.
(Howard:)Thanks, honey.
(Howard:)All right. What is your deal?
(Leonard:)Excuse me?
(Howard:)Inviting my girlfriend
to come see your electron accelerator?
Yeah, so?
Wow, you really are a piece of work.
(Howard:)It's not enough
you get the prom queen...